♪A light shines on me♪
نور يضيء علي ♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
ورقة تسقط على الأرض ♪
♪A person♪
شخص ♪
♪Living in another world♪
العيش في عالم آخر
♪A beating heart♪
قلب ينبض ♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪ رياح لطيفة ♪
♪You bring me the light♪
أحضر لي النور
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
الوقوع في الحب في لحظة ♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪ قصة تتكشف صفحة بصفحة
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
قلب وحيد يسخن ببطء ♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪ نجمة متلألئة ♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
متجه لمقابلتك ♪
♪You mean everything to me in reality or in my dreams♪
♪ أنت تعني لي كل شيء في الواقع أو في أحلامي ♪
=The Next Stop W= (Adapted from the TV series W – Two Worlds)
= المحطة التالية W = (مقتبس من المسلسل التلفزيوني W - عالمان)
=Episode 24=
= الحلقة 24 =
Dad.
أب.
Did something happen?
هل حدث شئ؟
Where did Jiang Zhe go?
أين ذهب جيانغ زهي؟
The comics ended.
انتهت القصص المصورة.
For some reason,
لسبب ما،
the two worlds completely lost their connection.
فقد العالمان اتصالهما تمامًا.
I tried to pull him back
حاولت أن أعيده
into the world in many ways.
في العالم من نواح كثيرة.
But nothing worked.
لكن لا شيء يعمل.
This is
هذا هو
the end of the story.
نهاية القصة.
Jiang Zhe
جيانغ زهي
gave up his life to save yours.
تخلى عن حياته لإنقاذ حياتك.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
I shouldn't have
لا يجب أن أمتلك
ever started this comic.
من أي وقت مضى هذا الفيلم الهزلي.
Yanzhu once said
قال يانشو ذات مرة
as long as she could enter the comic world,
طالما أنها تستطيع دخول عالم القصص المصورة ،
she wouldn't die in there.
لن تموت هناك.
So she won't die
لذلك لن تموت
if I take her there.
إذا أخذتها هناك.
Just draw it.
فقط ارسمها.
But when he took control over me,
ولكن عندما تولى السيطرة علي ،
the drawing tablet
لوح الرسم
got smashed.
تم تحطيمه.
No.
لا.
The murderer could enter your world,
يمكن للقاتل أن يدخل عالمك ،
so there must be a drawing tablet
لذلك يجب أن يكون هناك لوح رسم
in the comic world
في عالم الكوميديا
that is identical to this one.
هذا مطابق لهذا.
As long as I find it,
ما دمت أجده ،
she can be saved.
يمكن أن تخلص.
But the murderer died.
لكن القاتل مات.
And the comic
والكوميديا
is about to end.
على وشك الانتهاء.
If you bring me the drawing tablet,
إذا أحضرت لي لوح الرسم ،
you won't be able to come back
لن تتمكن من العودة
after the final chapter.
بعد الفصل الأخير.
I must save her
يجب أن أنقذها
no matter what.
بغض النظر.
Doctor.
طبيب.
She's seriously injured.
لقد أصيبت بجروح خطيرة.
Please save her.
من فضلك احفظها.
Freeze!
تجمد!
Stop there!
توقف هناك!
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
Please hang in there.
من فضلك انتظر هناك.
Please
لو سمحت
save her.
أنقذها.
Jiang Zhe.
جيانغ زهي.
You've been encircled.
لقد تم محاصرتك.
I love you.
أحبك.
I love you too.
أحبك أيضًا.
Jiang Zhe risked his life
جيانغ زهي خاطر بحياته
and got the drawing tablet
وحصلت على لوح الرسم
for me to change the plot
بالنسبة لي لتغيير المؤامرة
and wipe out the wound.
ويمسح الجرح.
That's why
لهذا
there isn't a single scratch on you.
لا يوجد خدش واحد عليك.
The murderer died.
مات القاتل.
Jiang Zhe was put in jail.
تم وضع جيانغ زهي في السجن.
The comics should end here.
يجب أن تنتهي القصص المصورة هنا.
The two worlds
العالمين
have lost connection.
فقد الاتصال.
You have to accept it.
عليك أن تقبله.
(From then on,)
(من ذلك الحين فصاعدًا)
(I've been writing down what I want to tell him)
(كنت أكتب ما أريد أن أقول له)
(on paper boats.)
(على قوارب ورقية).
(I believe)
(أعتقد)
(even though we're in different worlds)
(على الرغم من أننا في عوالم مختلفة)
(and dimensions,)
(والأبعاد ،)
(he will sense my love.)
(سوف يشعر بحبي.)
(I believe we'll)
(أعتقد أننا)
(see each other again.)
(نرى بعضنا البعض مرة أخرى.)
It's like a dream
انها مثل حلم
that we're finally together,
أننا أخيرًا معًا ،
looking at this world.
ينظر إلى هذا العالم.
Yeah.
نعم.
Ever since we met,
منذ أن التقينا ،
we've been pushed forward by something.
لقد تم دفعنا للأمام من خلال شيء ما.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
how I proposed to you
كيف اقترحت عليك
and offered you the ring
وعرض عليك الخاتم
in front of my home
أمام منزلي
with all the media people there?
مع كل الإعلاميين هناك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
what to do at that moment.
ماذا تفعل في تلك اللحظة.
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
I know
أنا أعرف
we've been
كنا
through a lot.
من خلال الكثير.
I know you care about the ceremonial touch in life.
أعلم أنك تهتم بالمسة الاحتفالية في الحياة.
I think
أظن
I should do a formal proposal.
يجب أن أقوم باقتراح رسمي.
Will you marry me?
هل ستتزوجني؟
Yes.
نعم.
(I've been to your world.)
(لقد كنت في عالمك.)
(Now)
(الآن)
(it's time for you to be in my world.)
(حان الوقت لأن تكون في عالمي.)
Hello, I'd like to pay.
مرحبًا ، أود الدفع.
Zhu, wake up.
تشو ، استيقظ.
Are you reading this comic too?
هل تقرأ هذا الفيلم الهزلي أيضًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Here.
هنا.
See you around.
أراك بالجوار.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Nice ring.
حلقة لطيفة.
♪Looking out at you from a lighthouse far away♪
ينظر إليك من منارة بعيدة ♪
♪Cupping a few rays of sunshine♪
الحجامة بأشعة الشمس المشرقة
♪Can it♪
♪ هل يمكن ♪
♪Warm your heart?♪
♪ تدفئ قلبك؟
♪The ties between people♪
الروابط بين الناس ♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪ لا تعد ولا تحصى ومعقدة ♪
♪As long as♪
♪ ما دام ♪
♪We hear♪
♪ نسمع ♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
دقات القلب والنفس لبعضهم البعض ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪ أنا في انتظار أن تستدير ♪
♪The world is silent and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪ العالم صامت وافتقد الصخب والضجيج
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪ ضع قلبي في خطوط راحة يدك ♪
♪The balance of the scales of love is tipped by you♪
ميزان موازين الحب يميل إليك ♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪ المس عالمك الداخلي ♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة خيالية ♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪ زوج من العشاق فقدوا عقولهم
♪And been sinking♪
♪ وتم الغرق ♪
♪In love♪
♪ في الحب ♪
♪The ties between people♪
الروابط بين الناس ♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪ لا تعد ولا تحصى ومعقدة ♪
♪As long as♪
♪ ما دام ♪
♪We hear♪
♪ نسمع ♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
دقات القلب والنفس لبعضهم البعض ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪ أنا في انتظار أن تستدير ♪
♪The world is silent and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪ العالم صامت وافتقد الصخب والضجيج
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪ ضع قلبي في خطوط راحة يدك ♪
♪The balance of the scales of love is tipped by you♪
ميزان موازين الحب يميل إليك ♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪ المس عالمك الداخلي ♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة خيالية ♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪ زوج من العشاق فقدوا عقولهم
♪And been sinking♪
♪ وتم الغرق ♪
♪In love♪
♪ في الحب ♪